Finding Aid for the Elizabeth Vann Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- PHOTOGRAPHS IN THE COLLECTION
  - (Box 48)
    - Class pictures, maps (Box 48)
Vann, Elizabeth. 1974: (1)n.d.(to Felix Vann); Aug*31(to Nina); Sept.12(to Felix),20(to Mary Bell), 20(Virginia Wright)(2); Oct.27(Virginia Danforth). F 15. Sept.21(Jane Sutherland). F 15.
Slosson, Lucy Denny Wright(Mrs. Preston). “In Memoriam” by Elizabeth Vann. 5 copies. F 16.
Slosson, Lucy Denny Wright(Mrs. Preston). Obituaries and Memorial Service. F 17.
Slosson, Preston William.
1928: July 28,31; Aug.8; Sept.26; Oct.10(Editor, The New Republic),14(Collins),17(Father & Mother),19; Dec.1,2.
1935: Apr.9(Prof. Mowat).
1948: July 15(Collins); Oct.4(Collins); Nov.9(Neil), 9(Alexander G. Ruthven),9(Lucy),ll(Lucy).
1954: May 23; July 4(Eugene Vann); Oct.25(1?.E. Shipley Nov.3,4,5(Mrs. Smith).
1956: June 25.
1958: Sept.1(Edith & Roscoe),12(Gordon).
1959: oct.17(Flora May & Wilhelm).
1961: Feb.23; Apr.4(Flora May).
1962: Jan.20(Edith),22(Edith & Roscoe); Feb.25; Mar.3(Edith),12; Apr.13.
1963: Feb.6.
1964: Nov.18.
1968: oct.4(Edith & Roscoe).
1970: Sept.4.
Incoming to Preston from R.B. Shipley. 1954: Oct.25. F 18.
Slosson, Preston William, continued: (2)n.d.
1972: Jan.22(May); Feb.14; July 15; Aug.16; Oct.2; Nov.8.
1973: Feb.9(Neil); June 25,29; July 11-16, 25,27(James G. Stahlman),28; Aug.2; Sept.7,11; Oct.24.
1974: Jan.17,28; Feb.15,21; Apr.1-8,11; May 12, 24,30; July 4,19-20; Aug.12,15(Editor, The Michigan Daily); Oct.6; Dec.13.
1975: Mar.11; Apr.23; May 10,19; June 3,24; July 11(Mr. Rotunno),19,28; Aug.23; Sept.5,23; Oct.12.
1976: Apr.6; May 15(Mrs. James G. Stahlman).
Incoming to Preston:
Macaulay, Angus H. 1975: Apr.16
Rotunno, Archie 1975: (July)
Staebler, Neil 1973: July 25
Stahlman, James G. e1973: Apr.28; May 5. F 19.
Slosson, Preston William. Articles, newscasts, political views. F 20.
Slosson, Preston William. Autobiography, A Teacher’s Report Card. 1975. “ Chapter 7, “Innocents Abroad.” Invitation to dinner in his honor. F 21.
Slosson, Mae Preston. Autobiography, 1857-1943. F 22.
Stephenson, Lucy Chase Wright(Mrs. Jim-Bob). (3)n.d., (2)n.d.(Lou & Pine), (l)n.d.(Mother, Daddy). 1954: Sept.5. 1960: Oct.5; Dec.10. 1961: Jan.16; Mar.15,15(Edith & Roscoe); Dec.12. (1) before 1965. 1974: Oct.2,4,15,21,24. F 1.
Bennett, Evelyn Stephenson(Mrs. Mark)”Evie”. (2) n.d. 1973: Wedding announcement. 1974: May 30; Dec.18. F 1.
McKeen, Lucky Stephenson(Mrs. Daniel). (3) n.d. ?: Son’s birth announcement. 1967: Wedding invitation. F 1.
Stephenson, John B. Newspaper clippings. F 1.
V
Vann, Bob & Joyce. 1973: Dec.11.
Vann, David & Lil. (l)n.d., (l)n.d.(Aunt Libby). Picture. 1973: Apr.27(Essie). 1975: Apr.12; Dec.l (Essie). DeJarnatt, Deborah Moore(Mrs. George), neice. (l)n.d.
1970: Wedding invitation. F 2.
Vann, Dorothea Deimel(Mrs. Felix H.).
1935: June 24; Sept.2,8,11; (l)n.d.
1969: Aug.26; Sept.29; Nov.30.
1970: Aug.29; Dec.8.
1971: Jan.16; Sept.6.
1972: ?(2); July 13,25; Aug.31; Sept.19; Nov.6.
1973: June 4.
1975: July 5. F 3.
(Vann), Frances. (l)n.d.; 1963: Nov.6; Dec.5. F 4.
1948: Jan.2. F 4.
Vann, Gene & M. Elsanna(Zane). (l)n.d.
1964: Dec.30.
1973: Sept.26.
1974: Jan.24; Mar.5. F 5.
Vann, Joel & Katherine. (2)n.d.
1964: Jan.12.
1973: Dec. 27.
1977: Feb.15. F 6.
(Vann), Madeline. 1963: Dec:30. F 7.
Vaughn, Ruby & Torn. 1976: Dec.?. 2 pictures. F 8.
Von Roth, Rosy. 1973: Sept.7. F 8.
W
White, Collins Denny & Martha Virginia Smith. (2)n.d.
1943: Apr.28(2),30; May 1,3,4,6,10.
1957: Feb.2.
1959: Aug. 25.
1961: Jan.8.
1964: ?. F 9.
White, Collins Denny, Jr. & Susan. 1959: Dec.19. F
White, Edith Allen Denny & Roscoe Marvin. (10)n.d.
1909: May 17.
1910: Apr.l(Mother); Sept.?(Mother).
1941: Oct.5; (Dn.d.
1951: July 5(Lucy).
1954: Mar. 26(Bettie White (Mrs. Marvin)); Nov.19.
1957: July 25(Margaret D.); Nov.21(2).
1959: Dec.10.
White, Edith Allen Denny, continued:
1960: Mar.29.
1961: Jan.9,14; Sept.5.
1962: Feb.18(Lucy); May 2(Bonds, Mercereau & Krebs).
1963: Jan.8; Feb.20; Mar.14.
1964: Jan.29; Feb.24,27; Apr.1(Elizabeth Whitfield); June 1.
1965: Jan.13,14; Mar.15(Lucy); May 16,17.
1967: June 23; July 17,22; Aug.1(2); Oct. 3,9,14.
1968: July 18; Mar.25. 30.
1969: Feb.25; June 8,10.
1971: Mar.16.
1973: Feb.21,23; Mar.18; May 15; Oct.17, 21(Slossons),29; Dec.11,17.
1974: Feb.8,9(Sheppy Vann),27; Apr.4,5(Lucy & Preston),17; May 16; June 18; July 27; Aug.1,7,20,26,30; Sept.28,30.
1975: June 7(Flora May),10,13; July 24; Dec.29(Essio)
1976: July 12(Dean (Tyson )); May 3l(Essie).
1977: Feb.8(Libba): Mar.30; Apr.4;Aug.8;Nov.25(Essie)
1979: Dec.(Friends). 1980: Dec.(Friends). F 10.
1973: Nov. 29(to Edith) from Rebecca Young. F 10.
White, Roscoe Marvin. Obituaries, Memorial service and articles about Edith and Roscoe White. F 11.
White, Marvin & Bettie.
1954: Jan.9,12(Edith).
1955: Sept.6,7(Slossons). F 12.
White, Carrie(Mrs. Joseph E.). 1963: Feb.5. F 12.
White, Roy. 1973: commencement invitation. F 12.
Whitfield, Elizabeth Denny Dixon(Mrs. Theodore Marshall).
1957: Jan.31(Mother,Margaret Dixon).
1962: Apr.13.
1973: Apr.29; Aug.17,27,30; Sept.10.
1974: Feb.4.
1975: Apr.11,21.
1976: May 19; Aug.3-6,26,31. F 13.
Winfree, Lucy Chapman White(“Lou”), Mrs. Rieves Westwood, Jr.(“Pine”). Newspaper clippings and church articles. 1945: June 3.
1959: Aug.22.
1977: Feb.7(Essie).
1967: July 6.
1969: Jan.12.
1976: Oct.2. F 14.
Woods, John & Alice. (2)n.d. 1965: Dec.7.
Kohl, Emily Woods(dau.). (l)n.d. 1974: Wedding announcement. F 15.
Worthington, Groover & Emily Ruth. 1964: Jan.13. F 16. Worthington, Tina. 1964: Jan.12. F 16.
Wright, Virginia(Mrs. John W.). (3) n.d.
1963: Jan.11.
1966: Sept.29.
1970: Feb.23.
1974: Apr.25; June 6,25; Sept.2.
1975: Mar.14.
1977: May 18(Felix). F 17.
Wolter, Ingeborg & Edwin. (l)n.d.
Wedding announcement.
1965: Daughter’s birth announcement.
1960: Aug.3.
1962: Aug,12(Slossons).
1965: Jan.11.
1973: Dec.?.
1974: Jan.28; June 17; Oct.9; Dec.?.
1975: May 26. F 18.
Wuellner, Flora May Slosson & Wilhelm. (l)n.d.; (6)n.d.(Edith & RoSco
1947: July 23.
1956: Sept.9; Nov.20.
1958: Dec.29(Edith & Roscoe).
1959: July 29.
1960: Oct.27; Nov.24.
1961: Jan.l(Margaret),3(Edith & Roscoe).
1964: Jan.l; Nov.l.
1965: Mar.27(Edith); Aug.17(Edith); Dec.12,28.
1966: Dec.31.
1967: June 14.
1971: Mar.16; Apr.21,
1974: Apr.3.
1975: Jan. 26; Feb.6; Aug.13. F 19.
Newspaper clippings.
1960: Daughter’s birth announcement.
1965: Daughter’s birth announcement. F 19.
Incoming correspondence from family, first names only:
Auntie Aunt Marie Dean (Tyson?)
Incoming Correspondence after her death in 1974:
Grandpa Margie Aunt Margaret
Hazel Marty Betty
Kathleen Marget Edith
Aunt Lina Faye F 20.
1941: Oct.14(to Dottie) from Libby
1975: Feb.ll(To John & Alice) from Leroy F 20.
- INCOMING CORRESPONDENCE FROM EUGENE ELLIS VANN.
  - 1906 - Mar. 1914 (Box 17)
  - Aug.9; Sept. ?,28; Oct. ?,2,3,7,10,16,20,269 Nov.3,5, 7,9,14,15,19(4;,21,25,26,29. F 1., 1906: (Box 17)
  - Dec. (4)n.d.,6,10. F 2., 1906: (Box 17)
  - Jan.1,10,(4)n.d. Feb.2,9,12,17,19,22,(14)n.d. F 3., 1907: (Box 17)
  - Mar. 8,10,12,14,17,19,21,23,25,28,31. F 4., 1907: (Box 17)
  - Apr. 3,10,11,13,14,17,18,20,23,25,26,28. F 5., 1907: (Box 17)
  - May 2,4,5,7,9,12,13,16,17,20,22,23,26. F 6., 1907: (Box 17)
  - June 25(3),26(2),27,28,29,30., 1907: (Box 17)
  - July 1,2,3,4,5,7,9,14,15,16,17,18,19,24,25,27,30,31. F 7., 1907: (Box 17)
  - Aug. ?,3,8,9,12,13,16,24-Sept.4., 1907: (Box 17)
  - Sept. 4,7,16,22,24,25,29(2). F 8., 1907: (Box 17)
  - Oct. 1,5,10,22-26,31., 1907: (Box 17)
  - Nov. 5,9,16,19,25,29. F 9., 1907: (Box 17)
  - Dec. ?,3,4,12,26., 1907: (Box 17)
  - Jan. 2, 9, 24., 1908: (Box 17)
  - Feb. 1,4,17., 1908: (Box 17)
  - Mar. 26,27,28,29,30(2),31. F 10., 1908: (Box 17)
  - Apr. 1,2,3,5,6,8,10,11,12,14,15,16,17,19,20(2), 21, 22,23,25,27(2),29. F 11., 1908: (Box 17)
  - May 1,2,3,4,5(2),6(2),7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14(2),15. F 12., 1908: (Box 17)
  - July ?,27,28,29,31(2)., 1909: (Box 17)
  - Aug. 1. F 13., 1909: (Box 17)
  - Aug. 16,23., 1910: (Box 17)
  - Sept. 12,23,30-oct. 1., 1910: (Box 17)
  - Oct. 12,23., 1910: (Box 17)
  - Nov. 9,17,20,21,27., 1910: (Box 17)
  - Dec. 5,7,25. F 14, 1910: (Box 17)
  - Jan. 3,7-16,25., 1911: (Box 17)
  - Feb. 11,23., 1911: (Box 17)
  - Mar. 12,20., 1911: (Box 17)
  - May 18., 1911: (Box 17)
  - Apr. 17. F 15., 1912: (Box 17)
  - (1)n.d., 1913: (Box 17)
  - Feb. 5,10,21,23., 1914: (Box 17)
  - Mar. 9,21-22,24. F 16., 1914: (Box 17)
- Apr. 1914 - 1964
  - Apr. 6,10,17,20,25., 1914: (Box 18)
  - May 4,16., 1914: (Box 18)
  - Aug. ?•, 1914: (Box 18)
  - Sept. ?,14,15,18. F 1., 1914: (Box 18)
  - Aug. 2; Nov. 23-Dec.1; Dec. 8., 1917: (Box 18)
  - Mar. 15; Apr. 14; May 3. F 2., 1918: (Box 18)
  - May 3, 1921: (Box 18)
  - Feb. 7., 1922: (Box 18)
  - Mar. 11,15,17,21,23,26,28., 1922: (Box 18)
  - Apr. 16,22,23., 1922: (Box 18)
  - Mar. 23-Apr. 24: Extracts from letters. F 3., 1922: (Box 18)
  - Nov. 21-22,29., 1922: (Box 18)
  - Dec. 1,6,9,12,17,24,25,26,30,?., 1922: (Box 18)
  - Jan. 4,6,10,18,23,28,?., 1923: (Box 18)
  - Feb. 4. F 4., 1923: (Box 18)
  - Jan. 23,27., 1924: (Box 18)
  - Feb. 1,6,11,14,21,29., 1924: (Box 18)
  - Mar. 7,16(2;,28., 1924: (Box 18)
  - Apr. 2,6,11,12,25., 1924: (Box 18)
  - May 2., 1924: (Box 18)
  - Sept. 29., 1924: (Box 18)
  - Oct. 2,30. F 5., 1924: (Box 18)
  - Dec. 25., 1925: (Box 18)
  - Jan. 2,7,8,17,23., 1926: (Box 18)
  - Feb. 5,10,11,13., 1926: (Box 18)
  - Nov. 27(2)., 1926: (Box 18)
  - Dec. 4., 1926: (Box 18)
  - Apr. 9,14,27. F 6., 1927: (Box 18)
  - Jan. 1,3,12,16,23,28., 1928: (Box 18)
  - Dec. 30., 1928: (Box 18)
  - Jan. 7(2),13,16,23,30., 1929: (Box 18)
  - Feb. 1,10,17,20,24,26., 1929: (Box 18)
  - Mar. 1,16,19,24,28., 1929: (Box 18)
  - Apr. 2,7,11,18,21,28., 1929: (Box 18)
  - Dec. 28. F 7., 1929: (Box 18)
- Apr. 1914 - 1964
  - Apr. 6,10,17,20,25., 1914: (Box 18)
  - Apr. 21,23,28., 1930: (Box 18)
  - May 6,10,12.23., 1930: (Box 18)
  - Nov. 5. F 8., 1930: (Box 18)
  - Jan. 9,12,16,23,27,29., 1931: (Box 18)
  - Feb. 3,12,22., 1931: (Box 18)
  - Mar. 2,3,5,6,10,16,20,22,?., 1931: (Box 18)
  - Apr. 3,5,10,18,22,25,27,29., 1931: (Box 18)
  - May 2,7. F 9., 1931: (Box 18)
  - Mar. 8,10,20,26,30., 1932: (Box 18)
  - Mar. 5. F 10., 1933: (Box 18)
  - Jan. 22., 1934: (Box 18)
  - 1934:, Feb. 23. (Box 18)
  - 1934:, Mar. 10,19,22,25. (Box 18)
  - 1934:, Apr. 5 ?. (Box 18)
  - 1934:, Nov! 7’,14,21,26,28,29. F 11. (Box 18)
  - Jan. 5,21,23,25,28., 1935: (Box 18)
  - Nov. 25,29., 1935: (Box 18)
  - Mar. 23. F 12., 1936: (Box 18)
  - May 2,3,9,14,25., 1937: (Box 18)
  - July 4,8. F 13., 1937: (Box 18)
  - June 27., 1938: (Box 18)
  - Feb. 26; Mar. 18,25; Apr. 6. F 14., 1939: (Box 18)
  - (2)n.d., 1940: (Box 18)
  - Mar. 26,28., 1940: (Box 18)
  - Apr. 1,3., 1940: (Box 18)
  - Sept. 5,7,11., 1940: (Box 18)
  - Oct. 10. F 15., 1940: (Box 18)
  - July 7., 1941: (Box 18)
  - Aug. 20,21,24., 1941: (Box 18)
  - Oct. 8,23,27,28., 1941: (Box 18)
  - Feb. 2,?., 1942: (Box 18)
  - Apr. 15., 1942: (Box 18)
  - May 20(2),21,?., 1942: (Box 18)
  - Oct. ?., 1942: (Box 18)
  - Nov. 12,13. F 16., 1942: (Box 18)
  - (4) n.d., 1943: (Box 18)
  - Apr. 10., 1943: (Box 18)
  - May 13,16,20,24,27,31., 1943: (Box 18)
  - June 3,7(2),16., 1943: (Box 18)
  - Sept. 18., 1943: (Box 18)
  - May 22,29,31., 1944: (Box 18)
  - Mar. 7,11,13,18,22,27,31., 1945: (Box 18)
  - Apr. 6. F 17., 1945: (Box 18)
  - Nov. 2,4,7,17. Apr. 10; May ?, 14., 1946: (Box 18)
  - Feb. 11,14; Aug. 2,4,5., 1948: (Box 18)
  - Apr. 7,8., 1950: (Box 18)
  - (l)n.d.; Aug. 11,12,16., 1952: (Box 18)
  - Nov. 7. F 18., 1955: (Box 18)
  - Jan. 17,21,24., 1958: (Box 18)
  - Feb. 4,5,7,13,28., 1958: (Box 18)
  - Mar. ?(2),7,10., 1958: (Box 18)
  - July 25. F 19., 1959: (Box 18)
  - Oct. 5,8,9,11,14., 1961: (Box 18)
  - Jan. 4., 1962: (Box 18)
  - July 10,14,16,19,20,21,23,26. Nov., 1962: (Box 18)
  - 16. F 20., 1962: (Box 18)
  - Apr. 1,4,7,9., 1963: (Box 18)
  - July 19., 1963: (Box 18)
  - Oct. 28,29,30., 1963: (Box 18)
  - Nov. 2,5,6,., 1963: (Box 18)
  - Dec. 30., 1963: (Box 18)
  - Mar. 5,6,7,9,11,12,16,17,18,20,21,23,26,27,30., 1964: (Box 18)
  - Nov. 2,4,5. F 21., 1964: (Box 18)
- INCOMING CORRESPONDENCE FROM FELIX HUFFMAN VANN.
  - 1922 - 1968 (Box 19)
  - (5)n.d., ? (Box 19)
  - Jan. 2; (1)?., 1922: (Box 19)
  - Feb. 18; Mar. 26; Apr. 2., 1929: (Box 19)
  - Mar. 2,9,17,22,29., 1930: (Box 19)
  - Apr. 8,13., 1930: (Box 19)
  - May 4, 2(2),17,23,26., 1930: (Box 19)
  - Nov. 9,15. F 1., 1930: (Box 19)
  - Feb. 9,23,27; Aug. 22., 1931: (Box 19)
  - Dec. 13., 1933: (Box 19)
  - Jan. 2,25; Apr. 6. F 2., 1934: (Box 19)
  - Sept. 23,25,30., 1934: (Box 19)
  - Oct. 7,13-14,21,28., 1934: (Box 19)
  - Nov. 5,11,18,24,25., 1934: (Box 19)
  - Dec. 2,9,16(2),20. F 3., 1934: (Box 19)
  - Jan. 6,11,13,18,20,24,27,28., 1935: (Box 19)
  - Feb. 3,10(2),17(2),22,25(2)., 1935: (Box 19)
  - Mar. 4,10(2),17,24,25., 1935: (Box 19)
  - Apr. 3,16,23,30., 1935: (Box 19)
  - May 7(2),14,21(2),24,29., 1935: (Box 19)
  - June 4,7,10. F 4., 1935: (Box 19)
  - June 17,24,30., 1935: (Box 19)
  - July 8,10,15,20,29., 1935: (Box 19)
  - Aug. 4,11,16,20. F 5., 1935: (Box 19)
  - Mar. 25., 1937: (Box 19)
  - Mar. 3; May 25., 1938: (Box 19)
  - Feb. 14., 1939: (Box 19)
  - Mar. 10,18,22,27., 1939: (Box 19)
  - Apr. 8,13., 1939: (Box 19)
  - May 23., 1939: (Box 19)
  - Mar. 30; Aug. 26; Sept. 2,6., 1940: (Box 19)
  - Aug. 21,24; Nov. 3. F 6., 1941: (Box 19)
  - July 18,20,24,29., 1942: (Box 19)
  - Aug. 3,9,20., 1942: (Box 19)
  - Sept. 2,6,11,15,29., 1942: (Box 19)
  - Oct. 9,17,23,30., 1942: (Box 19)
  - Nov. 3,6,12. F 7., 1942: (Box 19)
  - Feb. 21., 1943: (Box 19)
  - Apr. 8,14,21., 1943: (Box 19)
  - May 6(2),12,17,19,26., 1943: (Box 19)
  - June 7,9,14,20,29., 1943: (Box 19)
  - July 6,25., 1943: (Box 19)
  - Aug. 4,10,16,22,26., 1943: (Box 19)
  - Sept. 5,19,25., 1943: (Box 19)
  - Oct. 16,25., 1943: (Box 19)
  - Nov. 9,20,28., 1943: (Box 19)
  - Dec. 6,13,14,19. F 8., 1943: (Box 19)
  - Jan. 2,5,13,24., 1944: (Box 19)
  - Feb. 1,9,17,20,21., 1944: (Box 19)
  - Mar. 20., 1944: (Box 19)
  - Apr. 1,6,8.15,27., 1944: (Box 19)
  - May 4,13,16,20,22., 1944: (Box 19)
  - June 1,16,20,24,28., 1944: (Box 19)
  - July 3,9,16,23,29,31., 1944: (Box 19)
  - Aug. 5,8,14,18,28,30., 1944: (Box 19)
  - Sept. 8,15,24,29,30., 1944: (Box 19)
  - Oct. 8,10,16,23., 1944: (Box 19)
  - Nov. 5,10,15,20,26., 1944: (Box 19)
  - Dec. 2,5,10,19,20,25,29,31. F 9., 1944: (Box 19)
  - Jan. 4,7,12,15,21,29., 1945: (Box 19)
  - Feb. 4,11,20,25., 1945: (Box 19)
  - Mar. 11,17,22,23,30., 1945: (Box 19)
  - Apr. 8,16,19,26. F 10., 1945: (Box 19)
  - May 4,9,12-13,20,28., 1945: (Box 19)
  - June 4,10,24,30., 1945: (Box 19)
  - July 3,9,14,22,29., 1945: (Box 19)
  - Aug. 5,8,19,27., 1945: (Box 19)
  - Sept. 2,9,16,24., 1945: (Box 19)
  - Oct. 7,14,21,25,30., 1945: (Box 19)
  - Nov. 11., 1946: (Box 19)
  - Jan. 28. F 11., 1947: (Box 19)
  - July 27., 1951: (Box 19)
  - Aug. 8,17; Nov. 17,28; Dec. 7,21,31., 1952: (Box 19)
  - Jan. 6,18,25., 1953: (Box 19)
  - Feb. 8., 1953: (Box 19)
  - Mar. 7(2),21,31., 1953: (Box 19)
  - Apr. 13,17,24., 1953: (Box 19)
  - May 6,16,20., 1953: (Box 19)
  - June 1,8,12., 1953: (Box 19)
  - Aug. 7,17,24,27., 1953: (Box 19)
  - Nov. 4., 1953: (Box 19)
  - Aug. 4,12,20,26., 1954: (Box 19)
  - June 14; Aug. 6,23; Oct. 22. F 12., 1955: (Box 19)
  - Feb. 11; Mar. 17; Aug. 3,10,15,17., 1957: (Box 19)
  - Jan. 9,19; Feb. 10,24; Aug. 4(2),10,16., 1958: (Box 19)
  - Aug. 5,12,19,26., 1959: (Box 19)
  - Aug. 6,14,18,20., 1960: (Box 19)
  - Aug. 1,10,11,16., 1961: (Box 19)
  - Aug. 15,21., 1962: (Box 19)
  - Apr. 28; Aug. 6,9,21., 1963: (Box 19)
  - Feb. 15,18., 1964: (Box 19)
  - Apr. 6,9,17,23., 1964: (Box 19)
  - Aug. 3,8,10,12,15,19,24,26,28. F 13., 1964: (Box 19)
  - Feb. 20,24,26., 1965: (Box 19)
  - Mar. 1,4,6,7,9,10,11,12,14(2),18,22,26,29,31(2)., 1965: (Box 19)
  - Apr. 2,6,10,14,18., 1965: (Box 19)
  - May 1., 1965: (Box 19)
  - Sept. 16,19,26.29., 1965: (Box 19)
  - Nov. 28., 1965: (Box 19)
  - June 20,23., 1966: (Box 19)
  - July 9,21,22., 1966: (Box 19)
  - Aug. 8,15,22,25,29., 1966: (Box 19)
  - Sept. 4,9,20. F 14., 1966: (Box 19)
  - Jan. 15; Apr. 30; May 17)., 1967: (Box 19)
  - June 18,26., 1967: (Box 19)
  - July 3,12,16,22(2),27,29,31., 1967: (Box 19)
  - Aug. 3,7,11,19,23,26., 1967: (Box 19)
  - Sept. 2,10,12., 1967: (Box 19)
  - Nov. 1,6,11,12,14,18,27., 1967: (Box 19)
  - Dec. 3. F 15., 1967: (Box 19)
  - Jan. 12,14,21,28,31, 1968: (Box 19)
  - Feb. 2,4,17,18., 1968: (Box 19)
  - June 13,16,22., 1968: (Box 19)
  - July 1,5,12,16,19,27,30., 1968: (Box 19)
  - Aug. 7,16,22., 1968: (Box 19)
  - Sept. 4,13,17,21,26., 1968: (Box 19)
  - Oct. 7., 1968: (Box 19)
  - Nov. 10,30., 1968: (Box 19)
  - Dec. 3. F 16., 1968: (Box 19)
- 1969 - 1977
  - Jan. 5,16,24,29., 1969: (Box 20)
  - Feb. 5,14,24., 1969: (Box 20)
  - Mar. 4,12,31., 1969: (Box 20)
  - Apr. 9,14,20, 1969: (Box 20)
  - May 11,16,20,28., 1969: (Box 20)
  - June 1,6,14,24,28., 1969: (Box 20)
  - July 6,9,11,16,25(2),27,30., 1969: (Box 20)
  - Aug. 3,6,24,31., 1969: (Box 20)
  - Sept. 3,6,11,16,26., 1969: (Box 20)
  - Oct. 6,13,20,24,27., 1969: (Box 20)
  - Nov. 3,7,17,29., 1969: (Box 20)
  - Dec. 10,21,28. F 1., 1969: (Box 20)
  - Jan. 5,7,14,15,16,24,29., 1970: (Box 20)
  - Feb. 3,21,27. Mar. 2,7. Apr. 22,27., 1970: (Box 20)
  - May 2,6,10,17,24,29,30., 1970: (Box 20)
  - June 6,7,10,15,29., 1970: (Box 20)
  - July 1,4,7(2),25,26., 1970: (Box 20)
  - Aug. 1,5,8,13,19,20,23,26,31., 1970: (Box 20)
  - Sept. 2,16., 1970: (Box 20)
  - Nov. 19,22,29., 1970: (Box 20)
  - Dec. 8,?. F 2., 1970: (Box 20)
  - Jan. 3,23,30., 1971: (Box 20)
  - Feb. 7(2),8,13,19,24., 1971: (Box 20)
  - Mar. 16,22,25,28., 1971: (Box 20)
  - Apr. 18,25., 1971: (Box 20)
  - May 4,8,15,21., 1971: (Box 20)
  - June 3,8., 1971: (Box 20)
  - July 21,23,30., 1971: (Box 20)
  - Aug. 5,13,16,22,26,29., 1971: (Box 20)
  - Sept. 5,11,19,26., 1971: (Box 20)
  - Oct. 2,10,31., 1971: (Box 20)
  - Nov. 10,16,24., 1971: (Box 20)
  - Dec. 1,8. F 3., 1971: (Box 20)
  - Jan. 1,7,17,24,27., 1972: (Box 20)
  - Feb. 4,12,18,25., 1972: (Box 20)
  - Mar. 1,5,7,15,22,30., 1972: (Box 20)
  - Apr. 16,23,30., 1972: (Box 20)
  - May 18,27,31. June 22., 1972: (Box 20)
  - July 4,5,11,14,20,21,26,27,29., 1972: (Box 20)
  - Aug. 2,4(Dr. Robert E. Kahn),5,12,20,27., 1972: (Box 20)
  - Sept. 10,23., 1972: (Box 20)
  - Oct. 3,22,27., 1972: (Box 20)
  - Nov. 12,21,28., 1972: (Box 20)
  - Dec. 4,31. F 4., 1972: (Box 20)
  - Jan. 4,14,22., 1973: (Box 20)
  - Feb. 20,26., 1973: (Box 20)
  - Mar. 6,26., 1973: (Box 20)
  - Apr. 4,15,22,25., 1973: (Box 20)
  - May 10,13,24., 1973: (Box 20)
  - June 4,11,20,24., 1973: (Box 20)
  - July 7,27., 1973: (Box 20)
  - Aug. 3,6,10,28., 1973: (Box 20)
  - Sept. 3,11,19,30., 1973: (Box 20)
  - Oct. 7,14., 1973: (Box 20)
  - Nov. 1,8,11,22,26, 1973: (Box 20)
  - Dec. 3. F 5., 1973: (Box 20)
  - Jan. 12,16,23., 1974: (Box 20)
  - Feb. 7,17., 1974: (Box 20)
  - Mar. 7,12,21,27,31., 1974: (Box 20)
  - Apr. 7,13,21,28., 1974: (Box 20)
  - May 9,14,22,28., 1974: (Box 20)
  - June 9,16,21,25., 1974: (Box 20)
  - July 14,18,22,26,30., 1974: (Box 20)
  - Aug. 3,5,12,19,26,31., 1974: (Box 20)
  - Sept. 8,18., 1974: (Box 20)
  - Oct. 14,24,31(2)., 1974: (Box 20)
  - Nov. 9,21., 1974: (Box 20)
  - Dec. 15. F 6., 1974: (Box 20)
  - Jan. 5,19,27., 1975: (Box 20)
  - Feb. 5,17., 1975: (Box 20)
  - Mar. 14(pnone call),19,22,30., 1975: (Box 20)
  - Apr. 17,27., 1975: (Box 20)
  - May 2,10,23., 1975: (Box 20)
  - June 18,24,26., 1975: (Box 20)
  - July 4,7,12,16,21,26., 1975: (Box 20)
  - Aug. 2,8,16,21,30., 1975: (Box 20)
  - Sept. 2,7,14,23,24., 1975: (Box 20)
  - Oct. 29., 1975: (Box 20)
  - Nov. 21., 1975: (Box 20)
  - Dec. 7,8,20,31. F_£., 1975: (Box 20)
  - Jan. 4,17,20,25,28., 1976: (Box 20)
  - Feb. 1,4,11,17,21,24,26., 1976: (Box 20)
  - Mar. 5,15,29. Apr. 2., 1976: (Box 20)
  - May 6,16,23. F 8., 1976: (Box 20)
  - June 1,13,18,26,30., 1976: (Box 20)
  - July 5,10,14,17,24,30., 1976: (Box 20)
  - Aug. 2,7,11,18,21,25,29., 1976: (Box 20)
  - Sept. 4,13,19,28., 1976: (Box 20)
  - Oct. 21,28., 1976: (Box 20)
  - Nov. 7,12,16,20,28., 1976: (Box 20)
  - Dec. 4,10,11,17,25. F 9., 1976: (Box 20)
  - Jan. 1,11,12,15,24,29,30., 1977: (Box 20)
  - Feb. 11,17,23,27., 1977: (Box 20)
  - Mar. 7,10. F 10., 1977: (Box 20)
- INCOMING CORRESPONDENCE FROM FRIENDS.
  - Allen - Hutchinson (Box 21)
  - Allen, Dudley & Wilma. (2)n.d.; 1977: Feb.7. F 1. (Box 21)
  - Baillie Family: (Box 21)
    - Bose, Jean Baillie(Mrs. Henry ). 1974: Dec.?. 1977’- May 22. F 2. (Box 21)
    - Kimball, Astri Baillie(Mrs. John). (Box 21)
    - 1973: Wedding invitation. (Box 21)
    - 1975: Dec.13. F 2. (Box 21)
    - Kiphuth, Janet Baillie(Mrs. DeLaney). (2)n.d. (Box 21)
    - 1968: Mar.1,19. 1974: May 15. (Box 21)
    - 1976: Feb.11 - Press release. F 2. (Box 21)
    - Knapp, Catherine Baillie(Mrs. Clarence). (Box 21)
    - 1973: Jan.24; Feb.5. (Box 21)
    - 1974: Dec.16. (Box 21)
    - 1975: Aug.18,26; Nov.24. Wedding invitation from daughter, Catherine. Newspaper clipping of Catherine. (Box 21)
    - 1976: Wedding announcement from daughter Cynthia. (7)n.d. (Box 21)
    - (10n.d.(from daughter Catherine). F 2. (Box 21)
  - Barbosa, Carmen. (l)n.d. F 3. (Box 21)
  - Bastos, Guiomar. (l)n.d.; 1917: Jan.22; ?. F 3. (Box 21)
  - Bates, Pat(Mrs. William) (Box 21)
    - (l)n.d.. 1956: June 25. 1972: Sept. 24. 1973: Apr. 23; June 5. F 4. (Box 21)
  - Battle, Charles. 1907: Jan. 30. F 4. (Box 21)
  - Bender, Margaret.1969: Feb. 5. F 5. (Box 21)
  - Bennett, Charles & Catherine. (l)n.d. F 5. (Box 21)
  - Bingham, Ray & Emma. (Box 21)
    - (l)n.d. (Box 21)
    - 1973: Feb.15; Apr.17; July 14; Oct.10. (Box 21)
    - 1974: Jan.4; Feb.12,25; Mar.8; Apr.11; May 18; Oct.l (Box 21)
    - 1975: Apr.4,30; May 25: July 31; Sept.11,24; Oct.6,8. (Box 21)
    - 1976: Feb.29; Sept.2: Oct.19; (l)n.d. (Box 21)
    - 1977: Mar.15; Apr.11(to Edith White); May 19(to Felix); July 12(to Felix). F 6. (Box 21)
  - Bond family: (Box 21)
    - Bond, Mary. (l)n.d. (Box 21)
    - 1960: Jan.2. 1948: Jan.2. (Box 21)
    - 1969: Dec.9(to Felix). (Box 21)
    - 1973: May 16(to Felix). (Box 21)
  - Bond,Frank & Iris. 1975: Jan.2. (Box 21)
  - Bond Family, continued: (Box 21)
    - Bond, Kathleen. (6)n.d. (Box 21)
    - 1948: Dec.6. Jan.4. 1962: May 5. (Box 21)
    - 1964: Feb.19; Oct.29; Nov.9,1°. (Box 21)
    - 1965: Feb.15; Mar.9; May 26. (Box 21)
    - 1967: Aug.ll. (Box 21)
    - 1968: Feb.22. (Box 21)
    - 1969: Feb.22; June 27. (Box 21)
    - 197?: Aug.13. (Box 21)
    - 1970: Jan.17. (Box 21)
    - 1973: Dec.18. (Box 21)
    - 1974: Feb.26; Mar.5; Nov.4. (Box 21)
    - 1975: Jan. 13; May 9,27; June 12; July 23; Aug.27; Sept.?. F 7. (Box 21)
  - Bowden, Zelma. 1973: Dec.?; 1974”. Dec.25. F 8. (Box 21)
  - Bruce, Marylee(Mrs. J.L.). (l)n.d.; 1909: Dec.?(Mr.&Mrs. Collins Denny F 9. (Box 21)
  - Bryan, Fran 8c E.Kedar. (l)n.d.; 1973: Dec.?; 1974: Dec.?; 1975: May 28. F 10. (Box 21)
  - Burritt, Richard & Gertrude, (l)n.d.; 1972: Dec.?; 1977: Jan.2. F 11. (Box 21)
  - Caldwell, William A. (2)n.d.; 1963: Feb.25; 1971: May 12; 1976: Dec.9 (Box 21)
    - 1977: Mar.28(to Felix). (Box 21)
    - Newspaper clippings. (Box 21)
    - From Elizabeth Vann to Mr. Caldwell, 1963: Feb.12. F 1 (Box 21)
  - Carr, Helen. 1970: Nov.29; 1974: Nov.29; 1975: Feb.24. F 13. (Box 21)
  - D (Box 21)
  - Davies, Anne. (l)n.d.; 1958: Aug.17. (Box 21)
    - 1958: Granddaughter’s birth abbouncement. F 14. (Box 21)
  - Davis, Noah. 1909: Dec.?. F 15. (Box 21)
  - Davis, Vi & Tom. 1973”. Dec.?. F 15. (Box 21)
  - DeGraff, Margaret. 1964: May 23. F 15. (Box 21)
  - Denney, Ella Mae. (l)n.d.; 1974: Nov.29; 1975: Mar.8. F 16. (Box 21)
  - Denney, Frank P. 1956: Mar.5; 1973: Dec.28; 1974: Feb.3, Dec.? (Box 21)
  - 1975: Jan.l. Family picture. F 16. (Box 21)
  - Winters, Lillian Denney (Mrs. Harry). 1977”. Aug.l. F 16. (Box 21)
  - Dowds, Chuck & Ella.1967: Dec.?; 1969: Apr.20; 1972: Dec.? (Box 21)
    - 1973: July 16, Aug.22, Dec.4,15 (Box 21)